[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "House"]}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "Have you got any big scandals that you got up your sleeve for the next election campaign?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "any", "big", "scandals", "that", "you", "got", "up", "your", "sleeve", "for", "the", "next", "election", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "We're constantly working at least a half a dozen or so investigations at both the Senate and the House.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "constantly", "working", "at", "least", "a", "half", "a", "dozen", "or", "so", "investigations", "at", "both", "the", "Senate", "and", "the", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Which would you take?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "would", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Much bigger than that.", "answer_tokens": ["Much", "bigger", "than", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Do you think so?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "You think that's your lifelong contribution?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "that", "'s", "your", "lifelong", "contribution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I think it's a great contribution.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "contribution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "I said, my god, what greater compliment could they give me?", "question_tokens": ["I", "said", ",", "my", "god", ",", "what", "greater", "compliment", "could", "they", "give", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "JJR", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, OK, let me try and give you a better one because I think it's a fascinating thing when you look at your career.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "OK", ",", "let", "me", "try", "and", "give", "you", "a", "better", "one", "because", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "fascinating", "thing", "when", "you", "look", "at", "your", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Here you are, you're super rich, you've had this amazing life, but part for me things, if you had your time again, could you be tempted into a totally different path?", "question_tokens": ["Here", "you", "are", ",", "you", "'re", "super", "rich", ",", "you", "'ve", "had", "this", "amazing", "life", ",", "but", "part", "for", "me", "things", ",", "if", "you", "had", "your", "time", "again", ",", "could", "you", "be", "tempted", "into", "a", "totally", "different", "path", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "No, no, I don't have any regrets.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "regrets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "But what about for example the recent story of this pastor who came out with these outrageous comments -- mind you, outrageous because he made (INAUDIBLE) -- about wanting his right to burn the Quran and he then burns the Quran and as a result of that absolutely inevitably a lot of people get killed in Afghanistan?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "about", "for", "example", "the", "recent", "story", "of", "this", "pastor", "who", "came", "out", "with", "these", "outrageous", "comments", "--", "mind", "you", ",", "outrageous", "because", "he", "made", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "--", "about", "wanting", "his", "right", "to", "burn", "the", "Quran", "and", "he", "then", "burns", "the", "Quran", "and", "as", "a", "result", "of", "that", "absolutely", "inevitably", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "get", "killed", "in", "Afghanistan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "NN", ":", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, you pay a price for everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "pay", "a", "price", "for", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "That there should never be any limits?", "question_tokens": ["That", "there", "should", "never", "be", "any", "limits", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "I don't think you put any limits.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "put", "any", "limits", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "How do you feel about being an American right now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "an", "American", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I feel good about being an American.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "good", "about", "being", "an", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Did you have any sense as a big businessman this was going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "sense", "as", "a", "big", "businessman", "this", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "I think I did see it coming.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "did", "see", "it", "coming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I think morality is sometimes too subjective to define.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "morality", "is", "sometimes", "too", "subjective", "to", "define", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "I mean, where do your morals lie?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "where", "do", "your", "morals", "lie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Hey, I put on my clothes the same way everybody else does every day.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "I", "put", "on", "my", "clothes", "the", "same", "way", "everybody", "else", "does", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "What's your view, say, of sexual infidelity, for example?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", ",", "say", ",", "of", "sexual", "infidelity", ",", "for", "example", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Hey, look, I'm the first guy to defend the philandering president.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "look", ",", "I", "'m", "the", "first", "guy", "to", "defend", "the", "philandering", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "That's big problems for you?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "big", "problems", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "That's big trouble.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "big", "trouble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "You think people should leave him alone?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "people", "should", "leave", "him", "alone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I think it's a tragedy the way the media exploited him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "tragedy", "the", "way", "the", "media", "exploited", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "You're a bipolar yourself, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "bipolar", "yourself", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "What is the sign for you that says he is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "sign", "for", "you", "that", "says", "he", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, you know, the first sign is that you become euphoric, you know, about everything you do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "first", "sign", "is", "that", "you", "become", "euphoric", ",", "you", "know", ",", "about", "everything", "you", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "When did you first think that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "first", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, probably when I first started out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "probably", "when", "I", "first", "started", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Is there a lot of hypocrisy talked about the adult entertainment business, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "lot", "of", "hypocrisy", "talked", "about", "the", "adult", "entertainment", "business", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, hypocrisy is terrible throughout our society.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "hypocrisy", "is", "terrible", "throughout", "our", "society", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "It's just the hypocrisy we're going after, you know?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "the", "hypocrisy", "we", "'re", "going", "after", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "What you see, must (INAUDIBLE) to you.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "you", "see", ",", "must", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 203, "question": "I mean, if you had a daughter that wanted to become a porn star, what would you have said to her?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "if", "you", "had", "a", "daughter", "that", "wanted", "to", "become", "a", "porn", "star", ",", "what", "would", "you", "have", "said", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "That would be her business but we --", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "her", "business", "but", "we", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Is that always the case, Larry?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "always", "the", "case", ",", "Larry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Most of the time.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "of", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Isn't it up to you -- don't you have a slight moral responsibility to protect the more vulnerable girls who get hooked on this stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "up", "to", "you", "--", "do", "n't", "you", "have", "a", "slight", "moral", "responsibility", "to", "protect", "the", "more", "vulnerable", "girls", "who", "get", "hooked", "on", "this", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RP", "TO", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "We do.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Or are a classic repressed teenager before?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "a", "classic", "repressed", "teenager", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "I mean are you still as energized as you used to be, Larry?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "are", "you", "still", "as", "energized", "as", "you", "used", "to", "be", ",", "Larry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Yes, but got a few limitations on me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "got", "a", "few", "limitations", "on", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Who do you think has probably been more successful over the years, you or Hugh Hefner?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "has", "probably", "been", "more", "successful", "over", "the", "years", ",", "you", "or", "Hugh", "Hefner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hugh Hefner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Hefner is in his 80s now, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Hefner", "is", "in", "his", "80s", "now", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Think he's losing it.", "answer_tokens": ["Think", "he", "'s", "losing", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Icenbach"]}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "What have you found from your study of president's sex lives?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "found", "from", "your", "study", "of", "president", "'s", "sex", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "First of all, when I said I was going to do this book, I reached out to my friend David Icenbach with -- from the university because he's a history professor.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "when", "I", "said", "I", "was", "going", "to", "do", "this", "book", ",", "I", "reached", "out", "to", "my", "friend", "David", "Icenbach", "with", "--", "from", "the", "university", "because", "he", "'s", "a", "history", "professor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "What were the most shocking discoveries, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "most", "shocking", "discoveries", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Well, one thing that nobody knows, the youngest first lady was 19.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "thing", "that", "nobody", "knows", ",", "the", "youngest", "first", "lady", "was", "19", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Harding", "John Kennedy"]}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Who was the most sexually promiscuous president, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "was", "the", "most", "sexually", "promiscuous", "president", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "It does (INAUDIBLE) between Warren Harding and John Kennedy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "between", "Warren", "Harding", "and", "John", "Kennedy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "To you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["To", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "That's probably true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "probably", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 301, "question": "I mean, if you look at someone like Bill Clinton, for example, he's one of the most popular presidents ever, and yet he was a pretty naughty boy, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "if", "you", "look", "at", "someone", "like", "Bill", "Clinton", ",", "for", "example", ",", "he", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "most", "popular", "presidents", "ever", ",", "and", "yet", "he", "was", "a", "pretty", "naughty", "boy", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Yes, but see --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "see", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$85,000"]}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "WDT", "NN", "$", "CD", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Are you still investigating the sex lives of Republicans?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "still", "investigating", "the", "sex", "lives", "of", "Republicans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Every year, we're running an ad in the \"Washington Post\" that cost $85,000 to try to get as much dirt as we can on him.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "year", ",", "we", "'re", "running", "an", "ad", "in", "the", "``", "Washington", "Post", "''", "that", "cost", "$", "85,000", "to", "try", "to", "get", "as", "much", "dirt", "as", "we", "can", "on", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What makes you so confident that the Republicans that you're going to be exposing are any better or worse than Democratic rivals?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "you", "so", "confident", "that", "the", "Republicans", "that", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "exposing", "are", "any", "better", "or", "worse", "than", "Democratic", "rivals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBP", "DT", "RBR", "CC", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, we will expose anybody.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "will", "expose", "anybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "House"]}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Have you got any big scandals that you've got up your sleeve for the next election campaign?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "any", "big", "scandals", "that", "you", "'ve", "got", "up", "your", "sleeve", "for", "the", "next", "election", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "We're constantly working at least half a dozen or so investigation at both the Senate and the House.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "constantly", "working", "at", "least", "half", "a", "dozen", "or", "so", "investigation", "at", "both", "the", "Senate", "and", "the", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "So they'd all be Republicans, would they?", "question_tokens": ["So", "they", "'d", "all", "be", "Republicans", ",", "would", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "VB", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I -- most of them are Republican.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "most", "of", "them", "are", "Republican", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Well, what -- for arguments sake -- if you've got a story about President Obama, a sex scandal about him, would you feel it was right to publish that, given the obvious damage that would do to the country, and its reputation?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "--", "for", "arguments", "sake", "--", "if", "you", "'ve", "got", "a", "story", "about", "President", "Obama", ",", "a", "sex", "scandal", "about", "him", ",", "would", "you", "feel", "it", "was", "right", "to", "publish", "that", ",", "given", "the", "obvious", "damage", "that", "would", "do", "to", "the", "country", ",", "and", "its", "reputation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", ":", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I wouldn't want to, but I would.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "want", "to", ",", "but", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "You would?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Because it would be very hypocritical of me not to.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "would", "be", "very", "hypocritical", "of", "me", "not", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What do you feel when you look back on what happened to you that day?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "look", "back", "on", "what", "happened", "to", "you", "that", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I don't look at it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "look", "at", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WP", "RB", "PRP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Do you feel bitter about it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "bitter", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "LYNT: I don't look at who shot me -- whoever it was shot me.", "answer_tokens": ["LYNT", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "look", "at", "who", "shot", "me", "--", "whoever", "it", "was", "shot", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "It was an inter-racial photo shoot?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "an", "inter-racial", "photo", "shoot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RB", "VB", ",", "``", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Has it affected you in your spirit do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "affected", "you", "in", "your", "spirit", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "People always ask, \"What's it like being in that wheelchair?\"", "answer_tokens": ["People", "always", "ask", ",", "``", "What", "'s", "it", "like", "being", "in", "that", "wheelchair", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "I don't spend my life dwelling on anything I can't do nothing about.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "spend", "my", "life", "dwelling", "on", "anything", "I", "ca", "n't", "do", "nothing", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "As someone who fought to expand the parameters of free speech in a very good way.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "someone", "who", "fought", "to", "expand", "the", "parameters", "of", "free", "speech", "in", "a", "very", "good", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "How do you see where you've got to?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "see", "where", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "I look at the redemption as being able to tell my story, to find my voice and try to make a change in the lives of others, and hopefully inspire them to come forward too.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "look", "at", "the", "redemption", "as", "being", "able", "to", "tell", "my", "story", ",", "to", "find", "my", "voice", "and", "try", "to", "make", "a", "change", "in", "the", "lives", "of", "others", ",", "and", "hopefully", "inspire", "them", "to", "come", "forward", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "And this went on for how long?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "went", "on", "for", "how", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Till the age of 18.", "answer_tokens": ["Till", "the", "age", "of", "18", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "And how often was this happening?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "often", "was", "this", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "It varied.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "varied", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Where was your mother in all this?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "was", "your", "mother", "in", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "They divorced when I was 12 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "divorced", "when", "I", "was", "12", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Did you have even a tiny inkling about what might be happening?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "even", "a", "tiny", "inkling", "about", "what", "might", "be", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, we didn't meet until our junior year.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "did", "n't", "meet", "until", "our", "junior", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "You only found out about the abuse after Stacey finally shot her father?", "question_tokens": ["You", "only", "found", "out", "about", "the", "abuse", "after", "Stacey", "finally", "shot", "her", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stacey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Did you intend to kill him then?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "intend", "to", "kill", "him", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What happens then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "The gun was downstairs.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "gun", "was", "downstairs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "And you shot him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "shot", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "And I shot him.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "shot", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "He does what -- how does he react?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "what", "--", "how", "does", "he", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "He didn't realize he has been shot.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "realize", "he", "has", "been", "shot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "So what did you do?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "did", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I shot him a second time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "shot", "him", "a", "second", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "In the head this time?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "head", "this", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "I didn't know where it was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "know", "where", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "You were told not to by your legal team?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "told", "not", "to", "by", "your", "legal", "team", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "No, it's not that I wasn't allowed to.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "that", "I", "was", "n't", "allowed", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "You're how old now, 18, 19?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "how", "old", "now", ",", "18", ",", "19", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I was 18 when I committed the crime and I was 20 when I finally went to trial.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "18", "when", "I", "committed", "the", "crime", "and", "I", "was", "20", "when", "I", "finally", "went", "to", "trial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "And that moment when they say life with no parole, what are you thinking then?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "moment", "when", "they", "say", "life", "with", "no", "parole", ",", "what", "are", "you", "thinking", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "When they came back with guilty in the first degree, I knew that it would be life without parole.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "they", "came", "back", "with", "guilty", "in", "the", "first", "degree", ",", "I", "knew", "that", "it", "would", "be", "life", "without", "parole", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Some people were claiming you killed him for his money?", "question_tokens": ["Some", "people", "were", "claiming", "you", "killed", "him", "for", "his", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"]}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Tom, let me just ask you, when this all comes out and the trial comes out, at what point does Stacey tell you about the abuse?", "question_tokens": ["Tom", ",", "let", "me", "just", "ask", "you", ",", "when", "this", "all", "comes", "out", "and", "the", "trial", "comes", "out", ",", "at", "what", "point", "does", "Stacey", "tell", "you", "about", "the", "abuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Well, unfortunately when all this came out, I had already enlisted in the Navy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "unfortunately", "when", "all", "this", "came", "out", ",", "I", "had", "already", "enlisted", "in", "the", "Navy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stacey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What was it like, prison for you, knowing perhaps there was never going to be any way out?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", ",", "prison", "for", "you", ",", "knowing", "perhaps", "there", "was", "never", "going", "to", "be", "any", "way", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I always had hope, because I felt like when I went to trial, I made the right choice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "had", "hope", ",", "because", "I", "felt", "like", "when", "I", "went", "to", "trial", ",", "I", "made", "the", "right", "choice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 555, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "We filed a petition for clemency, not a pardon, not asking for full-out --", "answer_tokens": ["We", "filed", "a", "petition", "for", "clemency", ",", "not", "a", "pardon", ",", "not", "asking", "for", "full-out", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "You've never disputed killing your father?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "never", "disputed", "killing", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "And he believed you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "believed", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Do you blame her for what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "blame", "her", "for", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "No, I do not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "What should they do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Find your voice, tell.", "answer_tokens": ["Find", "your", "voice", ",", "tell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]